Love can change what we want… war can change who we are
In the Land of Blood and Honey is a drama, romance,
war film directed by Angelina Jolie.
During the Bosnian War, Danijel, a soldier fighting for the Serbs,
re-encounters Ajla, a Bosnian who's now a captive in his camp he oversees.
Their once promising connection has become
ambiguous as their motives have changed.
Ajla, played by Zana Marjanović.
Danijel, played by Goran Kostić.
Aleksandar, played by Branko Đurić.
Nađa, played by Džana Pinjo.
Durja, played by Miloš Timotijević.
Mitar, played by Goran Jevtić.
In the Land of Blood and Honey (Bosnian: U zemlji krvi i meda) is a 2011 war drama film written, produced, and
directed by Angelina Jolie, and starring Zana Marjanović, Goran Kostić and Rade Šerbedžija.
The film, Jolie's first commercial release as a director, depicts a
love story set against the background of the Bosnian War.
It opened in the United States on December 23,
2011, in a limited theatrical release.
The film explores themes of muslim, sibling relationship, bosnian
war (1992-95), united nations, woman director.
The tone is emotional.